This dataset was recompiled/integrated from historical maps and SPOT satellite images. 

The value of LU_TYPE in the dataset indicates different land cover classes.

LU_TYPE=01 for Forest class 
LU_TYPE=02 for Grassland class
LU_TYPE=04 for Agriculture land class
LU_TYPE=08 for Built-up land class
LU_TYPE=13 for Inland water class
LU_TYPE=26 for Bare soil class

For any technical question, please contact Dr. Yi-Ying Chen (yiyingchen@gate.sinica.edu.tw) at RCEC Academia Sinica, Taiwan.

